<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.10/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.10/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.10.xsd" version="0.10" xml:lang="en">
  <siteinfo>
    <sitename>Asteron Roleplay Minecraft Wiki</sitename>
    <dbname>asteronroleplayminecraft</dbname>
    <base>https://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.fandom.com/wiki/Astoren_Roleplay_-_Minecraft_Wikia</base>
    <generator>MediaWiki 1.19.24</generator>
    <case>first-letter</case>
    <namespaces>
      <namespace key="-2" case="first-letter">Media</namespace>
      <namespace key="-1" case="first-letter">Special</namespace>
      <namespace key="0" case="first-letter" />
      <namespace key="1" case="first-letter">Talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="2" case="first-letter">User</namespace>
      <namespace key="3" case="first-letter">User talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="4" case="first-letter">Asteron Roleplay Minecraft Wiki</namespace>
      <namespace key="5" case="first-letter">Asteron Roleplay Minecraft Wiki talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="6" case="first-letter">File</namespace>
      <namespace key="7" case="first-letter">File talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="8" case="first-letter">MediaWiki</namespace>
      <namespace key="9" case="first-letter">MediaWiki talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="10" case="first-letter">Template</namespace>
      <namespace key="11" case="first-letter">Template talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="12" case="first-letter">Help</namespace>
      <namespace key="13" case="first-letter">Help talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="14" case="first-letter">Category</namespace>
      <namespace key="15" case="first-letter">Category talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="110" case="first-letter">Forum</namespace>
      <namespace key="111" case="first-letter">Forum talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="500" case="first-letter">User blog</namespace>
      <namespace key="501" case="first-letter">User blog comment</namespace>
      <namespace key="502" case="first-letter">Blog</namespace>
      <namespace key="503" case="first-letter">Blog talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="828" case="first-letter">Module</namespace>
      <namespace key="829" case="first-letter">Module talk</namespace>
      <namespace key="1200" case="first-letter">Message Wall</namespace>
      <namespace key="1201" case="first-letter">Thread</namespace>
      <namespace key="1202" case="first-letter">Message Wall Greeting</namespace>
    </namespaces>
  </siteinfo>
  <page>
    <title>(Character) Issac Guerk</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2150</id>
    <redirect title="(Character) Isaac Guerk" />
    <revision>
      <id>4129</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T04:47:49Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>SoldierIR10 moved page [[(Character) Issac Guerk]] to [[(Character) Isaac Guerk]]</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="37">#REDIRECT [[(Character) Isaac Guerk]]</text>
      <sha1>219p3q4rtpdhokplnxepv5sl2alkby9</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>(Character) Soldier Collencze</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2143</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4294</id>
      <parentid>4130</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-09-06T16:43:44Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>/* Background and Characteristics */</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="284">{{Template:Infobox character
|title = Soldier Collencze
|image = Collencze.png
|imagewidth = 250
|position = General-Secretary (Leader) of Esteria
|age = 32 years old
|status = Alive
|height = 5.11ft
|weight = 168lbs}} 


==Background and Characteristics==

==Other Characters==
  </text>
      <sha1>06p78vqr3vungthclobcji3q3gh9u1x</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Anarchism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2153</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4137</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T05:19:06Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:600px-Anarchy-symbol.svg.png|thumb|left]]                  ==Definition of: Anarchism==   Anarchism is a political ideology associated with the belief of no establishme...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1447">[[File:600px-Anarchy-symbol.svg.png|thumb|left]]

















==Definition of: Anarchism==


Anarchism is a political ideology associated with the belief of no establishment of government, no regulatory system of law and boundries, no authority and no forced participation. Anarchism also can systematically in theory work as a anarch-commune in which a community works together in the means of production and developing the world without any representative or dictatorial leadership. Many anarchists are associated with violent activities most of the time in acts against the state. Militant anarchist groups carry out acts of sabotage towards government industry, civil service and military these being the more extreme form of anarchists who do not tolerate apparatus of the state (public services). In corresponding to Socialist principles, anarchism advocates the destruction of class hierarchy. In it's own principles it believes of self-government, voluntary institutions and is against the systematic principles of collectivization and conscription, etc.

In times of the early 20th century and the First World War, Anarchists have been pro-war in countries where a monarchy is present. During wartime a monarchy is in vulnerable to revolution and anarchists take advantage of this therefore taking a pro-war stance. Anarchists have proven to use these opportunistic methods, and so say, so have all revolutionary groups in particular.</text>
      <sha1>sq5a2sg3nrr3s33wj8ac1fhn0x5rbjh</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Annexation</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2175</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4189</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-06T04:22:30Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:7544340_orig.jpg|thumb|left|Invasion of Poland September 1st, 1933]]             ==Definition of: Annexation==   Upon invasion of a city state, country or nation and wh...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="736">[[File:7544340_orig.jpg|thumb|left|Invasion of Poland September 1st, 1933]]












==Definition of: Annexation==


Upon invasion of a city state, country or nation and when successful, annexation occurs through imperialistic means to merge that state with the successing state, this can happen through compromise or violent means. Through violent means annexation always creates a reaction of many nationalists and natives of the annexed country in which resistance occurs and uproar. A country or state that is being annexed is found to be usually weaker than the successor. An example of compromise annexation is Anschluss of Germany and Austria during the Nazi period which was a creation of a marriage between the two states. </text>
      <sha1>l3izcwsdt22urr25434hp2hcftvyxtk</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Asteron Roleplay Minecraft Wiki</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2218</id>
    <redirect title="Astoren Roleplay - Minecraft Wikia" />
    <revision>
      <id>4289</id>
      <timestamp>2014-09-06T14:31:15Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>SoldierIR10 moved page [[Asteron Roleplay Minecraft Wiki]] to [[Astoren Roleplay - Minecraft Wikia]]</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="48">#REDIRECT [[Astoren Roleplay - Minecraft Wikia]]</text>
      <sha1>fsapz0c9ws45fl3cbfi41b8fx14j63m</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Astoren Roleplay - Minecraft Wikia</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>1461</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4323</id>
      <parentid>4322</parentid>
      <timestamp>2017-03-10T15:41:41Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>/* (Page setup/Lore creation by: SoldierIR10 Lore-Dev of Astoren Roleplay) */</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="8315">
&lt;mainpage-leftcolumn-start /&gt;



&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:20px;&quot;&gt;Astoren Roleplay Minecraft Wikia [Asteron RP]&lt;/span&gt;

== Alternative Historical 1960's Heavy Roleplay on Minecraft. ==

===(Page setup/Lore creation by: SoldierIR10 Lore-Dev of Astoren Roleplay)===

===(Owner of Astoren Roleplay: thesuperguy150)===

''===Welcome!
The server was first set up in late June 2014 by (minecraft alias) thesuperguy350. His counterparts responsible for the upbringing at the start being Lilbren, SL_Unknown, Priest_Leonardo, SoldierIR10 (Me), vorox97, Craftin_Craft etc. The lore implemented to expand the background of the foundation roleplay element of the server has been articulated by the founding community and myself as the Lore-Dev.===''

'''L O R E'''

June 1957, the state of Esteria, a republic led by an assemble of politicians who are keen on rigging the elections, especially in a state of low internal affairs checks in it's judiciary and public services. The ruling class party, they being the neo-conservatives, the unofficial opinion poll on them around the districts showed it all, they were clearly hated. A country with heavy industry and a large working class was enough for a foundation of rebellion. The leading party officials of the neo-conservatives; Nver Glacian, Ista Gronza and Tozla Murick, all in reality were just wealthy embezzling elitists of the state. 

In the same year, the Republic of Indronzia is hit with an economic crisis, the banks handing out loans as if they were free candy as a primitive method to encourage capital in the sector of commerce led the state into a recession when those businesses failed to repay. Gross Domestic Production fell as loans were restricted to individuals and industries, therefore workers were made redundant, unemployment began to rise dramatically. Indronzia was led by an elitist Liberal government that happened to betray principles of how taxation was to be dealt with and how their economics should have been managed. The midst of this crisis led to rising support for the Ultranationalists inside of Indronzia.

Meanwhile in Esteria the neo-conservatives drew harsh taxes on the working class, handing business grants to manufacturers such as Kreftin Steel Co. and State Purpose Supplements Corporation. Companies that provided the state Gendarmeriewith high quality grade provisions of armour apparrel and military grade weapons. Their job was to protect the state and corporations. When Indronzia went into economic downturn, Esteria's top priority trading partner was lost. Indronzia produced necessary foreign imports to Esteria of foodstuffs to encourage the non-essential commerce market and also it's food processing industries therefore dragging Esteria down with Indronzia. As Esteria felt the same repercussions when mistakenly Esterian National Banks tried to bail out Indronzia National Banks in the process, it drove itself down into a stage of depression.

The Proletarian Party of Esteria (PPE) formed in 1927 as a paramilitary party, membership began to rise as jobs became scarce. The aristocracy was leading itself into a dangerous situation as the trickle-down economics they had been using as a quick solution brought living conditions for the working class to it's knees. Indronzia, a country with a lot of nationalistic pride were hit with the cut-down of their military personnel. The likes of ceremonial events funded by Eskravz (the government administration and building.) as miniscule of an issue it may be,  in times of growing depression the people of Indronzia turned to the rhetoric of the ultranationalists.  These were the foundations for two wide-scale revolutions. Members of the Esterian gendarmerie even had felt outraged towards the undemocratic government of Esteria. As PPE entryists sunk into the gendarmerie without check, they inspired influence of their manifest. The gendarmerie leadership therefore were subdued. The revolution in Esteria sparked as Esteria went to war against Navarozta over dispute of emmigration problems in Esteria when refuge was accepted in Naravozta in 1962. By 1964 Esteria had suffered the revolt in the midst of war from it's own troops and gendarmerie as rations depleted and the war not being entirely justified.

The move of revolt sealed an alliance between the New Socialist Republic of Esteria between the Libertarian Republic of Navarozta as the military disobedience to the state was recognised, removing the neo-conservative elitists from power. Indronzia in the year of 1962 had a general election that won the ultranationalists the majority in the Indronzian parliament and the legitmacy to allow them into power. It wasn't that had, these two nations were obviously unstable and were too blindsided to defend themselves from a violent or deviant overthrow. However the ultranationalists wanted to maintain their right to rule. The ultranationalists were referred to as the Indronzian Nationalist People's Party, they rose to power with the support of three fifths of the Indronzian people and the Conservative Party who were sworn opponents of the Liberal government. 

The Republic of Indronzia was then formed into the People's Republic of Indronzia in September 1963. The new titles were wrote and a new map drawn as the Socialist Republic of Esteria claimed over territories the city-state of Kenetz and Festera through the means of passive invasion. Indronzia doing the same with the town and nation states of Kovmovo and Stenskt. All through the means of passive invasion, these states could not fend off these forces therefore were in automatic submission. Esteria granted the old defected Gendermerie a respective place in the main authority of the state. The old Gendarmerie was then renamed to the State Gendermerie of Esteria (SGE). It was used to protect the Esterian people and to ensure there was no anti-state activity. When Soldier Collencze rose to the leadership of the state of General-Secretary, the state then grew totalitarian in it's actions.

In the present times, the states with the polarized ideals become tense and suspicious of each other. With only the fundamental resources left of the old establishments, they both stay inert to political discussions or military actions as they like-mind both plan on industrializing their countries once again after the destruction of the old establishments economies. The misfortune of this however is they have reached the era of the youth breaking from their old traditions into the new punk/psychedelic music generation which influenced the youth of this era to involve themselves in libertarian and anarchist protesting, taking drugs, setting up illegal concerts and gigs. A time of authoritarianism and the struggle for freedom. With the ill-prepared Esteria and the ill-prepared Indronzia, two nations in the planet that are significant, currently tense with each other as formerly confirmed. In the development of intelligence agencies to carry out around the back operations, the era starts off cold.&lt;blockquote&gt;[It is now the year 1967, September. The planet is known as Astoren of alternative history. Closely relates to earth-based 60's known as the &quot;Swinging 60's&quot;]&lt;/blockquote&gt;

==Blurb - Links==




[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Nations Nations Category]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Characters Characters Category]


==Archive News from June/July server term.==
Four archived from the prior lore.

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Newspaper_22th_July_1960_(2014) Newspaper of 22th July 1960 (2014)]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Newspaper_of_24th_of_July_1960_(2014) Newspaper of 24th July 1960 (2014)]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Newspaper_of_26th_July_1960_(2014) Newspaper of 26th July 1960 (2014)]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Newspaper_of_28th_July_1960_(2014) Newspaper of 28th July 1960 (2014)]

==Latest activity==

&lt;activityfeed&gt;&lt;/activityfeed&gt;

&lt;mainpage-endcolumn /&gt;

&lt;mainpage-rightcolumn-start /&gt;

Photos and videos are a great way to add visuals to your wiki. Find videos about your topic by exploring Wikia's [[w:c:video|Video Library]].


&lt;mainpage-endcolumn /&gt;
[[Category:Browse]]
[[Category:Nations]]
[[Category:Characters]]</text>
      <sha1>gw947d2mh6kivl8x0l0cz8zzc8nvieq</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Autocracy</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2162</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4159</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T13:15:44Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Apftw8.jpg|thumb|left|274px]]             ==Definition of: Autocracy==   Autocracy is a system of rule in government, it is a dictatorially rule by one person or in a s...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1272">[[File:Apftw8.jpg|thumb|left|274px]]












==Definition of: Autocracy==


Autocracy is a system of rule in government, it is a dictatorially rule by one person or in a single-party state to rule by decree and authoritarian rule of supreme power. Other elements of autocracy can be martial law or a Fascist, Absolute Monarchist or Stalinist regime however these regimes don't need to be autocratic. Most autocratic regimes contain a high level of authoritarianism and usually contain total control policies. Most autocratic regimes form out of the dissolvement of parliament or puppeteering parliament and creating a law to rule by decree through parliamentry intimidation. Under autocratic rule there is no bureaucracy or commitee that keeps laws in check as it's an absolute dictatorial rule therefore no legal restraints whilst rule by decree is carried out which justifies how dangerous autocracy can be.

Elitist aristocratic nations require a power structure for them to be able to rule, therefore most autocratic regimes are anti-capitalist and probably lean to Fascism, Nazism or Stalinism. It is said that if there was to be conflicting debates between two nations at the risk of a war, an autocratic one would multiple the amount of violence as the outcome.</text>
      <sha1>g9u5qb2brm5l1k7czldtuu0anmctw5i</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Capitalism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2170</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4174</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-06T02:55:48Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Medium_capitalism.jpg|thumb|left]]                   ==Definition of: Capitalism==   Capitalism is an economic system in which the means of trade, industry and the mean...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1484">[[File:Medium_capitalism.jpg|thumb|left]]


















==Definition of: Capitalism==


Capitalism is an economic system in which the means of trade, industry and the means of the production are in the hands of private owners in their aspirations to create profit. Profit on the other hand being a very important element to capitalism is the accummulation of wealth by the formulae of: cost of the production of the product -&gt; sell the product for a higher price than it cost you to make it = profit. Capitalism consists of wage labour also in which the working class have only their labour to sell in goal to obtain money for themselves. In modern day capitalism wages have began to decrease as corporations begin to become more prominant and now have created wage poverty and bankrupcy of other competitive markets.

Capital or money (monetary system) is used for the exchange of goods and services, it's a monetary system which merits the value of labour therefore the entitlement of buying goods with money. In capitalism there is a hierarchy structure which consists of; Working-class (proletariat), the middle-class (petty-bourgeois) and the business-man class or capitalist class (bourgeoisie). The lowest class is the one that does all the industrial and commercial labour, the middle class carries out running small businesses, services and companies, the capitalist class consists of large corporations and fossil fuels services that own vast amounts of land and wealth.</text>
      <sha1>q3lip9g5ovw9nonwx0eae34birp80zi</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Characters</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2135</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4295</id>
      <parentid>4293</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-09-06T16:45:48Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>/* Leaders: */</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1350">==Characters - Category==


[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Asteron_Roleplay_Minecraft_Wiki#Asteron_Roleplay_Minecraft_Wikia_.5BAsteron_RP.5D Back home]


There is real players of the community that play their own significant character on a significant role within the community within roleplay. They are either leaders are famous societal figures within the community from their roleplay contributions and probably refered to by state officials or are state officials. This category page will present names of significant people that are leading figures of nations, groups, art or profession that is well known to the community. Characters as legitimate players of the community, players can get their character up onto the wikia if they make themselves well known with the innovation of effort and dedication to contribute a piece to the flowing history of the server.  Characters can be interesting to develop people's roleplay standards towards other characters, their personality and background branches out to much more interaction and therefore a very vital element to a roleplay server's appeal.


==Leaders:==
[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/(Character)_Soldier_Collencze Soldier Collencze - General Secretary of the Esterian Socialist Republic]

&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:20px;&quot;&gt;Significant Persons:&lt;/span&gt;</text>
      <sha1>2urycz8s200z8g2m0w31qbjuy0qf5c3</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Communism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2166</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4168</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T14:01:37Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:CommunismFlag.png|thumb|left]]         ==Definition of: Communism==   Communism is a socialist system that abolishes private property and has the working class of facto...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1047">[[File:CommunismFlag.png|thumb|left]]








==Definition of: Communism==


Communism is a socialist system that abolishes private property and has the working class of factories and farms collectively own the property and share it among each other. In Communism there is no state, no money or social classes, everything is based upon workers collectively working together and sharing resource to an abundant level. Instead of being known as state-ownership of property, this is called common ownership which deters the emergement of corporations and monopolization. Communist society is mean't to be that work is necessary for survival and not a choice whether or not to do it. Communism is mainly frowned upon by moderate and revolutionary socialists for this rhetoric therefore it is mainly false when socialism is compared to this relevant system.

Bear in mind, this is the true state of pure communism, the USSR had never formed this system it had only formed a Stalinist deformed Socialist state due to conflict with the transition theory.</text>
      <sha1>n9p84bwv3xw0uuaorjrn7uw9cdql4sp</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Conformity</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2190</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4222</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-14T01:12:45Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Brainwashing.jpg|thumb|left|308px]]               ==Definition of: Conformity==   Conformity is a term used politically for those who are defect to a totalitarian and i...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="653">[[File:Brainwashing.jpg|thumb|left|308px]]














==Definition of: Conformity==


Conformity is a term used politically for those who are defect to a totalitarian and informer regime. Authoritarian governments expect that their citizens conform to a lifestyle that they may wish or not that benefits the state as a form of distraction but high level of support towards the state. Confomity just means 'obey' by the norms and principles put in place by the authority that orchastrates it. Extreme conformation can usually mean someone is a loyalist of the regime or entirely brainwashed. Brainwashing occurs during indoctrination (see Propaganda).</text>
      <sha1>nht3zj47tyjxb72xota0jj6knaegtgy</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Conservatism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2217</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4277</id>
      <timestamp>2014-08-04T17:11:02Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:1353079287_5779_elephant.jpg|thumb|left]]           ==Definition of: Conservatism==   Conservatism is the idea of promoting the maintainance and conservation of traditi...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1387">[[File:1353079287_5779_elephant.jpg|thumb|left]]










==Definition of: Conservatism==


Conservatism is the idea of promoting the maintainance and conservation of traditional social institutes and policies. Conservatism withholds neo-classist views, traditionalist views and is opposed to modernism. Progress is normally withheld back under a Conservative government as they wish to maintain old forms of rule, architecture and development. The traditional values that conservatism may want to keep is a Constitutional Monarchy leading as Head as State if the case, the rights of women in which are reduced more than mens, maintaining the idea of the family roles and also ceremonial traditions are encouraged among the populace. 

Conservative economics usually is concentrated on support for the Corporations and the Big Businesses, the tax towards businesses is lower than towards the working class as the formulae to this idea is to tax the working class at a higher rate than business so that businesses can be provided grants in the incentive to create more jobs and workplaces in benefit to the working class. In argument this tactic has failed however is still at use, especially in times of recession or depression conservative governments would wish to implement austerity measures and cuts to public services and health services as a means to somehow 'save the economy'.</text>
      <sha1>0ad1r2v8jpol0s51l702w9993cfyn4s</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Crafting</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2199</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4263</id>
      <parentid>4242</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-07-26T21:40:27Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>/* Crafting */</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="876">==Crafting==


[[File:PKP_Recipe.png|thumb|left]]PKP Machine Gun - Recipe

Ammo: Golden Nuggets







[[File:M1911_Recipe.png|thumb|left]]M1911 Handgun - Recipe

Ammo: Golden Nuggets







[[File:Frag_Grenade_Recipe.png|thumb|left]]
Frag Grenade - Recipe









[[File:SV98_Recipe.png|thumb|left]]SV98 - Recipe

Ammo: Golden Nuggets







[[File:AKM63_Recipe.png|thumb|left]]AKM - Recipe

Ammo: Golden Nuggets







[[File:Leather_Recipe_Custom.png|thumb|left]]Leather Custom - Recipe









[[File:Olympia_Recipe.png|thumb|left]]Olympia Shotgun - Recipe

Ammo: Golden Nuggets







[[File:Riotgun_recipe.png|thumb|left]]Riotgun - Recipe

Ammo: Golden Nuggets







[[File:Saddle_Recipe_Custom.png|thumb|left]]Leather Saddle - Recipe









[[File:TearGas_Recipe.png|thumb|left]]Teargas - Recipe









[[File:String_Recipe_Custom.png|thumb|left]]String - Recipe</text>
      <sha1>kxa88qip5q1s19yfj6uwitp29pc8sh1</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Democracy</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2164</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4164</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T13:43:16Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Ballot-box.gif|thumb|left]]           ==Definition of: Democracy==   There are two types of democracy, Direct and representative. Democracy basically just means the peo...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1387">[[File:Ballot-box.gif|thumb|left]]










==Definition of: Democracy==


There are two types of democracy, Direct and representative. Democracy basically just means the people of the country are able to equally (sometimes unequally) can vote who they want to represent them in government. It can be to independant representatives to political parties, democracy also allows for the parliament to be kept in check so that also democratically laws can be passed by legal restraint to ensure no inappropiate legislation (law or regulation) is passed. That is representative democracy however, Direct Democracy is when the people gather during a schedueled event can decide directly what policies should be introduced as opposing to have representatives carry that out for them.

Suffrage is a term used for the enablement of voting, universal male suffrage just means that all males can vote, universal sex suffrage is when all genders can vote. Normally when Republics start out with a fundamental build to democracy it is republic governments that will introduce suffrage through parliament. They can determine the age when a voter can vote at and what gender they have to be to vote, even what class they must be and social status for that matter. Democracy can be manipulated to a degree of having a form of sinister control over a populace, this can be called an elitists autocracy.</text>
      <sha1>clloxgr9nbhmrbvdrl8juiekotrcddz</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Esterian Socialist Republic</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2221</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4312</id>
      <parentid>4311</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-11-11T10:27:16Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="464">'''Socialist Republic of Esteria'''

''Motto: &quot;May we triumph, as victorious Workers we are!''

''Demonym: Esterian''

''Government: Marxist-Leninist Single-Party State''

''Head of Government (First Secretary): First Secretary Collencze''

''Military: Esterian Soviet Army''

''Logistics Authority: State Office of Trade, Transport and Immigration''

''Upper House Legislative: Soviet Ministry of Esteria''

''Lower House Legislative: Province Council Authority''</text>
      <sha1>oegyreebl3om82mjayldjihhltfe8mn</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Fascism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2172</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4177</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-06T03:22:40Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:90px-Fascist_symbol.svg.png|thumb|left|Fasces (Old Roman symbol for authority)]]           ==Definition of: Fascism==   Fascism is an extreme and ultimatum of a nationa...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1875">[[File:90px-Fascist_symbol.svg.png|thumb|left|Fasces (Old Roman symbol for authority)]]










==Definition of: Fascism==


Fascism is an extreme and ultimatum of a nationalist authoritarian government to radical measures. It's oppositions are toward traditional conservatism, liberal, syndicalism and Marxism. Under Fascism policies such as totalitarian control can occur to intervene in the lives of the classes under the ruling class, such as forced participation in labour leagues and the removal of workers rights through industries and so on. Fascist states also intervene into industries and workplaces by the use of a corporate system to incorporate workers and employers together to create the illusion of democratic workers control which corporations would be named fascist syndicates or unions.

The principles of Fascism are not quite officially and normally abstract however Fascism inherits militaristic and ultranationalist ideas in which goes to the extent of the goals of autarky (self-sufficiency) and a non-immigrant state that does not include foreign elements (see National Socialism/Nazism). The foreign policy of Fascism is extremely aggressive and commonly uses the means of preparing war production to create a stronger and larger nation, Fascism leans towards imperialist tendencies as a matter to unify it's community under extreme nationalism. 

The leadership of Fascism has always led to autocratic dictatorial rule without the use of parliament, it takes upon the principles of social-darwinism in which the weak shall perish and the strong shall truimph. There is mainly a heavy presence of propaganda, restraint on intellectual or seditious material and authoritarianism. Education is mostly concentrated on physical, military and political education to create a regimentation of the youth for the future of a strongly militarized nation.</text>
      <sha1>sz7i4okjnlpn6lg5drmf8ah8ta5fvyz</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Feudalism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2177</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4192</id>
      <parentid>4191</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-07-06T06:51:07Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <minor/>
      <comment>SoldierIR10 moved page [[Fuedalism]] to [[Feudalism]]</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1220">[[File:Feudalism3.jpg|thumb|left]]








==Definition of: Feudalism==


Feudalism is a system dominent in the 9th and 15th centuries, it was based around structuring society around relationships in the exchange for land and services. In the hierarchy there was the King, the Royals and claimaint, the landlords, the knights and the peasants (serfdom). In Feudalism it was structured through military obligations of three concepts consisting of lords, vassals and fiefs. Vassals are those under ths subordinance and obligations of a Lord to carry out duties for that Lord. A lord is an individual within Feudal society who has been granted authority in the Kingdom he is bound to. A fief is a grant of territory or land that a lord has been prized with the authority over the land, the rents, taxes and serfs (slaves to the land).

Feudalism is mostly situated with early time absolute monarchies and mostly endevoured in constant blind warfare with no political compromise other than just blatant warfare. Feudalism has required warfare to sustain itself financially, to annex territories to expand it's wealth and influence and over time develop into a country in which it naturally moves onto a more advanced system.</text>
      <sha1>lhl5emwte23mrpf4mo86yjqhrjnk6e5</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Fuedalism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2178</id>
    <redirect title="Feudalism" />
    <revision>
      <id>4193</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-06T06:51:07Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>SoldierIR10 moved page [[Fuedalism]] to [[Feudalism]]</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="23">#REDIRECT [[Feudalism]]</text>
      <sha1>gi4b8fiepdshw987mz2tg90rx7n78ze</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Genocide</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2205</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4252</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-25T12:02:53Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Polish_Voluntary_II_Death_Squad_in_Lviv_1920.png|thumb|left|SS- Einzatzgruppen Death Squad]]               ==Definition of: Genocide (Systematic)==   Genocide is the or...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="898">[[File:Polish_Voluntary_II_Death_Squad_in_Lviv_1920.png|thumb|left|SS- Einzatzgruppen Death Squad]]














==Definition of: Genocide (Systematic)==


Genocide is the organized cleansing or killings of a ethnicity, group or nationality through organized elite militaries known as Death Squads, genocide is normally originated from National Socialism, Fascism, neo-Bolshevism and oligarchical collectivism. Euthanasia can also be referred to as genocide as it is the mass killings of elder or sick people. Most genocide either situates a chamber that then is flooded with hazardous instant death gasings or mass graves in the death squad carries out killings through shooting the group of people dead into the mass grave. This has been used prominantly over the periods of 1930's-1960's over the Nazi Germany regime, Soviet Union, Cambodia's Pol Pot regime, China's one child policy and so on.</text>
      <sha1>snmqqctvpwn9yknd6jlux6njvml3yf9</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>H.S.I.</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2220</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4307</id>
      <timestamp>2014-11-11T10:16:02Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;'''Hera Soldiers of Indronzia'''  In Greek mythology that somehow lurks in the alternative world of Astoren. The wife of Zeus, Hera had been a jealous type of character with g...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="755">'''Hera Soldiers of Indronzia'''

In Greek mythology that somehow lurks in the alternative world of Astoren. The wife of Zeus, Hera had been a jealous type of character with good reason as Zeus would carry out his love affairs elsewhere in which Hera decided to lead a revolt against Zeus that involved poisoning him. The group HSI unfortunately ill-educated in the Greek literature, just had only used the title to portray some form of profound rebellious character that wants to remove the current dominion they live under.

Even though under a Populist government, the HSI are a far-right nationalist socialist organization that adapts very fascist principles and known to be a very strongly aggressive organization. They are however without manifesto.</text>
      <sha1>ssuhsklt4o429may47c9z47uaqczgqn</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Imperialism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2180</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4201</id>
      <parentid>4200</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-07-06T21:32:42Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1330">[[File:195340810_orig.jpg|thumb|left|Picture that portrays historical Imperial Britain]]















==Definition of: Imperialism==


Imperialism is a country, nation or empires aspirations of conquest to extend authority over other independant countries to annex them, merging them into their Empire. Imperialism can consist of the slavery of the natives there or the purge of natives there to implement that nations own nationals as settlers on the occupied land. Regressive imperialism being defined of pure conquest is when that imperial nation carries out the atrocities to benefit their own nationals and selves in wealth, resources and land. The progressive form of imperialism is when an imperial nation attempts to expand it's influence of civilization to benefit those countries &quot;so they say&quot;.

Imperialism with the invasion of a country can lead to divisions within the nation and create political splinters of defecting extremists of nationlists and conforming extremists of loyalists to the imperial regime. In nationalist terms of those victim to imperialism would refer to imperial presence as an 'occupation' and will refuse to recognize the states new authority. Imperialist countries establish their own military, government and police into the countries they occupy to maintain their authority and influence.</text>
      <sha1>n2c6aqn1kubnbsh9hr059syhvqewdbq</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Main Page</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2128</id>
    <redirect title="Asteron Roleplay Minecraft Wiki" />
    <revision>
      <id>4062</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-04T17:37:29Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>CreateWiki script</username>
        <id>929702</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>CreateWiki script moved page [[Main Page]] to [[Asteron Roleplay Minecraft Wiki]]: SEO</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="45">#REDIRECT [[Asteron Roleplay Minecraft Wiki]]</text>
      <sha1>csmrmky98qdayr351ihamnefmw5qep6</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Martial Law</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2188</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4219</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-14T01:03:07Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Thugs-vs-people_1.jpg|thumb|left|334px]]               ==Definition of: Martial Law==   Martial Law is simple, a primitive policy to explain. If the local civilian or s...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="879">[[File:Thugs-vs-people_1.jpg|thumb|left|334px]]














==Definition of: Martial Law==


Martial Law is simple, a primitive policy to explain. If the local civilian or state government, maybe even the countries government fails to function in the matters in which is should. Martial Law is initiated within the state to maintain control over the populace by force and curfew in the matter of a strong threat of state of a emergency or terror threat. Martial Law however should not be confused by a military coup (see Coup d'etat). During martial law, executive power is removed from the government and the juridiciary. Military presence is heavy and by realistic explaination there is the presence of Armed Personnel Carriers (APC's), military off-roads and armed soldiers present on the street as a form of physical authority also known as &quot;having presence '''felt'''&quot;. </text>
      <sha1>g9ur1rl1n0w92y0953emo2al52cbjg3</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Militant Organizations</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2140</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4306</id>
      <parentid>4305</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-11-11T10:08:44Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>/* Lists; Paramilitaries, parties and resistance */</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1724">==Militant Organizations, Resistance and Political Factions==


This section is dedicated to the information of resistance and militant groups associated with the nations on the server and formed out of the conditions of the lore. These militant groups can be associated with allegiance to the state or against the state for their political goals. Resistance groups however play the role of not political goals of establishing their form of rhetoric but to restore liberty and democracy whilst in the period of being under a totalitarian and authoritarian regime, to resist conformation to legalistic laws and oppression. This provides information about their political agenda, their goals, their resistance purpose, their tactics, their history, their actions, their figures, etc. 

This allows for players to motivate themselves of getting range of goals set up in either passive or militant aggressive form to contribute events to the server, as the server does not want to plan events, the server wants events to happen naturally. Militant organizations can allow for terrorist events, resistance events of spreading anti-state messages, revolution, coup d'etats. Political factions can be parties that are repressed from any form of democratic power under the totalitarian era who attempt to spread their doctrine to influence a new agenda and to motivate their doctrines into a proletarian revolt. They can spread political literature, create anti-state posters and even create a manifesto. These are the opportunities that are presented by the roleplay fundamentals. 


==Lists; Paramilitaries, parties and resistance==

- Republican Liberation Front of Esteria [[R.L.F.E.]]

- Hera Soldiers of Indronzia [[H.S.I.]]</text>
      <sha1>5vts6izt14mrkxh210s5n2vrk67e0xc</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Mini Dictionary</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2151</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4279</id>
      <parentid>4278</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-08-04T17:11:34Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>/* A-F */</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="2136">==Alphabetical==
Everything in the dictionary is improvised from knowledge and wrote by the creator of this page, there has been no copying and pasting of any other's material on this wikia other than only being the no intentional plagiaristic use of the pictures as use as example however pictures with the T. Moore signiture on it drawn in the characters section is in ownership to the author of this wikia.

==A-F==


[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Anarchism - Anarchism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Annexation - Annexation]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Autocracy - Autocracy]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Conservatism - Conservatism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Communism - Communism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Conformity - Conform]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Capitalism - Capitalism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Democracy - Democracy]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Fascism - Fascism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Feudalism - Fuedalism]

==G-L==

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Genocide - Genocide]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Imperialism - Imperialism]

==M-R==

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Martial_Law - Martial Law]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Monarchism - Monarchism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/National_Socialism - Nazism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Populism - Populism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Propaganda - Propaganda]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Revolution - Revolution]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Republic - Republic]

==S-W==
[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Stalinist_Communism - Stalinism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Socialism - Socialism]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Totalitarian/Totalitarianism - Totalitarianism]

==Y-Z==</text>
      <sha1>2zoj2dyaa3c8mzztf8j2hh8sdlgfnuw</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Monarchism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2156</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4146</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T05:41:59Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Monarchism.jpg|thumb|left]]                ==Definition of: Monarchism==   A monarchy is when the head of state is either a King or Queen depending on the claimant who ...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1240">[[File:Monarchism.jpg|thumb|left]]















==Definition of: Monarchism==


A monarchy is when the head of state is either a King or Queen depending on the claimant who granted the seat in the Royal Family bloodline of the country. An absolute monarchy would have absolute control over the country it is head of state in, a constitutional monarchy would co-exist with a representative government in which it's powers are limited. Monarchies are known to be the biggest landowners and rent collectors in their country and the Royal Family of the Monarch inherits vasts amounts of wealth from this. Monarchies were very prominent in times of fuedalism and now only pose a traditional conservative element of government as a method to boost tourism under capitalism. 

A monarchist however is a person of that country who supports the monarchy they live under, this is quite common among patriots and loyalists of the state. Patriots being proud of their country and dedicated towards it, loyalists being loyal to their country's traditional form of rule and traditional society. Most of these traditionalist political ideals are mostly refered to as backwards living and can inherit principles of homophobia, anti-women and xenophobia.</text>
      <sha1>ip8qqajh73ti0jukk9nkgyquksjmleh</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>National Socialism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2186</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4216</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-14T00:54:07Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Nazism_09.jpg|thumb|left]]             ==Definition of: National Socialism (Nazism)==   National Socialism is derived from the principles of fascism, ultranationalism a...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="3055">[[File:Nazism_09.jpg|thumb|left]]












==Definition of: National Socialism (Nazism)==


National Socialism is derived from the principles of fascism, ultranationalism and socialism however National Socialism also appoints it's opposition towards Bolshevikism, Leninism and Marxism on Socialist ideologies therefore not of pure socialism. It had emerged officially through the early 30's in Germany in which became Nazi Germany. It's principles associate with a totalitarian state (total control over the lives of people) with the use of secret police, the removal of freedom of speech, and constant propaganda and indoctrination. It's principles extent to the idea of lebensraum (living space) of creating a large empire, extreme nationalism in which only the nationals of the country are provided privillaged rights and are treated as superior by the state, foreigners are either oppressed, deported or eradicated. Nazism has inherited anti-Semitism as a rhetoric scapegoat to get into power and also with the use of socialist policies in it's rhetoric to achieve power through the support of the majority of the people in the country.

In National Socialism, social-darwinism is taken into account in which the strongest is the fittest and will truimph, the weak shall die off. Forced assisted death of the old, the weak and disabled is known as euthanasia and National Socialism has practiced this policy in the past in noticable levels. It is an autocratic ideology that dissolves all democratic elements, it believes in a strong military and a strong perfected race of it's own. The education system within Nazism is altered to fit the believes of the state, anti-Nazi material is found to be majorly removed. Military education and political education that suits the needs of the state is only taught, religious education is removed as deemed unnecessary. Eugenics education is introduced by the state to teach a artificial lecture that the mixing of races can cause defects and that only the master race of the states fundamental base can only mix with itself as it is somewhat 'superior'.

National Socialism by leadership is ran by dictatorship, oligarchy and meritoracy. The resistance against these kind of governments are found to be very little as the informer state seems to portray a strong sense of paranoia and distrust in which resistance is repressed quite easily especially if the Nazi state is strong with special paramilitaries that the state creates. Youth under a Nazi state are completely regimented up until they are a young adult in which they are introduced into the military. The women under a Nazi state are made completely inferior and vessels to impregnation for the service to the state of increasing birth rates, women are seen as to be domestic apparatus in a Nazi state in which they shall serve only under the authority of the state and their husband. Intellectuals under a Nazi state would find themselves targetted and removed by the state either by torture and deportation which is highly unlikely, or death.</text>
      <sha1>n5w2aafbb4spdp346nhc7vmgh4w5thn</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Nations</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2134</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4324</id>
      <parentid>4297</parentid>
      <timestamp>2017-03-10T15:42:19Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>/* Countries of Brinonia and Venitica */</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="918">

In the year 1967, countries Esteria and Indronzia in times of a regional depression and dysfunctional elitist governments of those countries take a turn for the worst with the insurrection of Esteria and the legitmacy brought to the ultranationalists of Indronzia. The countries already bound to a harsh corrupt societies lead to the totalitarian changes in their reigns, exacerbating the countries liberties and conditions. The subversion of the Indronzian Liberal government and democracy led to the perish of the parliamentry system, leading to the state of Indronzia being led by decree, Esteria created a poster face Soviet-democracy with no function so that Central Government dictatorship could evolve and state bureaucracy granted power of the local of Esteria.
==Countries of Esteria and Vandoria==


[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Esterian_Socialist_Republic Esterian Socialist Republic]</text>
      <sha1>0ijwr5kmq1nu0my391elzg54fawa3pu</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Newspaper 22th July 1960 (2014)</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2202</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4245</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-22T16:33:38Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;==Independent Times Newspaper==  ===Rise in Esterian Military Membership===   This week of events has been very active, the Esterian Military confronted Kryturian police at th...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="3910">==Independent Times Newspaper==

===Rise in Esterian Military Membership===


This week of events has been very active, the Esterian Military confronted Kryturian police at their homefront in regards to confiscating their weapons as a radical act towards the vulnerability of the regimes defense. The Esterian Military have been making significant growth in membership which even the Esterian Government find becoming an issue whilst being without manual labourers. However the introduction of martial law into workplaces, the addition of labour is being provided by the military as a form of duty to maintain their occupations instead of being left with an empty agenda. The growth has lead up to six-seven active service units (server is in a small playerbase at the moment), this being significant to the widespread populace. Their activities have been involved in primary labour inside of mineshafts that the Esterian Military have established for the growth of materials they require for their weaponary in purpose of defense and operations. 20th July of this year, 1960 the Esterian Military have been given independence in their operations under the command of Commissar Indigo Bearings, whilst still having to obtain their official orders from the Esterian Government. Indigo Bearings was made Commissar around 18th July, in which he has led a professional elite of soldiers within the Soviet military of Esteria.

19th July, The State Security Commission, Esteria's state militia or police force as rather to be called had been made active with the appointment of a professionally experienced individual by the name of Nikolai Lobschevsky as now known to be called Commissioner Lobschevsky. His work has been efficient in direct request for the requirements of his force in which he is comparable to the same performance of Indigo Bearings, two gentlemen of prestige. Lobschevsky has been hard at work in sorting out the Headquarters and takes into account that the citizens of the state require satisfactory work to keep them occupied and to aspire in prosper. The set up of report and logistics offices within the SSC has enabled Lobschevsky to hire workers who will be involved in the checkings of records, reports and the logistics of their armory and necessities. The SSC will also be involved in Social Welfare work in which they will have to keep accounts on the provision of foodstuffs to enable those who are refugee's or nomads to be provided with necessary essentials even especially the Esterian people in times of crisis in which the SSC will be looking after the Esterian citizens by providing them sufficient rations that technically shall not be referred to as rations as it is sufficient.


===Kryturia under attack!===


18th July 1960, the Esterian Military came to the Kryturian lines to confront the Kryturian authorities in the confiscation of their weapons. This action was not without justification however. The Esterian Government had been getting reports of the inputs of Kryturian citizens arriving inside the borders of Esteria without any Esterian pass papers or passports. The Esterian government also found the individuals of Kryturian identidy to be as known as malicious persons. The Esterians took action and had the confisication of on hand weapons as a message to say &quot;If you cannot maintain your own people, we will take what identifies your authority&quot;. In the midst of all the fuss, a reactionary organization with no name identified appeared from out of the blue, automatic weapons had been fired indiscriminately into both confronting parties in which the Esterian military made evasive action and pulled away from the Kryturian lines, Kryturian officials faced casualties to the attack of the resistance group, they had been carrying PKP Heavy Machine Guns, suppressive weaponary which had also inflicted it's shooting towards civilian individuals of Kryturia.</text>
      <sha1>ogbjcb2x3n2xx0s4xiuv2z4baratb60</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Newspaper of 24th of July 1960 (2014)</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2203</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4248</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-25T11:53:35Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;==Independent Times Newspaper ==  ===Peace Talks Go Forward, Until the worst happens.=== The Kryturian main leader Henry Derse accepts peace talks with Esterian Military Comm...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="2594">==Independent Times Newspaper ==

===Peace Talks Go Forward, Until the worst happens.===
The Kryturian main leader Henry Derse accepts peace talks with Esterian Military Commissar Indigo Bearings and General-Secretary (Leader) Soldier Collencze, on the afternoon of 24th July 1960 these talks were carried out. The terms had been a compromise that both nations were to agree to a truce and ceasefire. Followed by a debate speaking of the guerrilla forces present in both nations and  about the collaboration with guerrila forces will not be tolerated in the conflict. The meeting was then disrupted when an explosive device went off in Inzatza Road Apartment Complex B talking out the whole alignment of the stairwell. The guerrila forces had then taken upon carrying out a terrorist act within the state of Esteria the capital city Menzia. Esterian Military personnel were sent to investigate however whilst unarmed, were underfire by feral Kryturian bodyguards who were primitive members of the Sylvania Liberation Army, the terrorist force carrying out the attack. All representatives were evacuated in Esterian aircraft to be presented to safety at Mount. Benzfor Esterian Airforce Base.


===Esterian Metro Service===
The Esterian Metro Station has now been completely finished for it's first stop, now residents (citizens) and tourists can board the express metro to the industrial/residential sector and town of Kenetz which has been left just entirely of roads and footpath so in which citizens with a good collection of wealth and aspirations can carry out constructing a factory of the production of their choice or business. Kenetz also gives any new citizens opportunities to set up housing there in which they are able to live from without the city of Menzia. The Metro Tunnel is connected from two points of travel, Menzia Station and Kenetz Station, in future plannings there will be a micro-instalment of small station in the agricultural town just outside of Menzia. 


===Terrorist Attack Hits Kryturia===
The Sylvanian terrorist organization of the SLA carried out a chemical attack towards the nation of Kryturia, as being a ideological opposite to the nation of Esteria, the Esterian Airforce sent a NBC team to the grounds of Kryturian to carry out an evacuation and cleaning operation as found entirely hazardous to environment maybe leading to inhabitation in the future. The Esterian Government allowed for the motion to be put forward. It has been currently unknown what device was used, who carried out the attack. The clearing has not been finished unfortunately.</text>
      <sha1>1nosr7rk7b37ubylv7119yrazthtl3e</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Newspaper of 26th July 1960 (2014)</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2213</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4265</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-26T21:53:41Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;==Independent Times Newspaper of 26th July 1960 (2014)==  ===Resistance base found underground in Kryturia!===   The Esterian Military on a black operation on the night of 26t...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1837">==Independent Times Newspaper of 26th July 1960 (2014)==

===Resistance base found underground in Kryturia!===


The Esterian Military on a black operation on the night of 26th July 1960 carried out a sabotage operation of the resistance group the Sylvanian Liberation Army, their base was then was bound with controlled explosives to sabotage the accommodation. The base was completely vaporized by the destruction. The Kryturian officials unaware of this incident had taken the opportunity to loot out the rest of technologies left within the base. The resistance had made no reactionary response, the Esterian Military had proven a show of extreme force that was enough to claim a superior position of the resistance organization. This was evidential to stating this was their central command accommodation. 


===Branfor Arms emerges!===


A social-cooperative factory had been set up by Esterian citizen Alex Branfor, a loyalist to the Esterian nation set up his industrial settlement in the town of Kenetz, a town bound to the jurisdiction of Esteria. Kenentz was set up after the completion of the Metro Link. The production of arms however are very equalized as Kryturian and Esterian states are allowed to buy from the industrial company. The weapons company began selling battle rifles to the Esterian military at high prices for their renown strength and therefore becoming a trend within military establishments. Most sharpshooters have taken liking to the production of Branfor Arms SV-Rifles. 

Two more citizens had moved to Kenetz close to the foundation of the Branfor Arms therefore showing the attraction of security that provides, the citizens have made inquiry to the concern of the industry and now enabling the provision of employment to the citizens of Esteria other than just being recruited into the military.</text>
      <sha1>1dwq3repajcdzaw4w8sx5reehiz37bx</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Newspaper of 28th July 1960 (2014)</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2215</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4274</id>
      <timestamp>2014-08-01T23:39:32Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;==Independant Times Newspaper of 28th July 1960 (2014)== ===Esterian/Katatlo Agreement of Katatlo Occupation=== General-Secretary, leader of Esteria Soldier Collencze on the 2...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="2640">==Independant Times Newspaper of 28th July 1960 (2014)==
===Esterian/Katatlo Agreement of Katatlo Occupation===
General-Secretary, leader of Esteria Soldier Collencze on the 28th of July had requested a meeting with the Katatloan leader known as Maid. During the meeting there was discussion with the recent events of threats delivered to the Katatloan administrative. The Esterian Forces were given the go ahead to enter Katatloan territory and set up a Forward Operating Base to establish alliance occupational control in the Katatloan land. This is a safeguard firewall of military support agreed upon the both leaders and also has granted the jurisdiction of authority with Katatlo for the time-being until compromise has been alternated. At this moment in time Esterian Troops have been relayed the messaged of advance into Katatlo with passive approach to occupy in a friendly manner. This has also been refered to as many analysis as Esterian strategical move to get a foothold advantage over the Kryturian Front but this was before the collapse of the Fascist regimen until it became a Constitutional Monarchy.


===The Fall of Fascism in Kryturia===
Leader Henry Derse of Kryturia had suddenly resigned his post and fled after conclusion to realising his dysfunctional regimen, his administrative was lacking and dissolved. The position was quickly taken as a military junta by Commissioner Reinhold who had then established a Populist Dictatorship in the first run. Reinholds structures of government developed and led to establishing himself as the Kaiser Reinhold creating a Constitutional Monarchy. The rise of military personnel and weapons production had then sprung within Kryturia's industrial and military sector. The people of Kryturia became satisfied to a fully innovated government ready to plan out necessities.


===Leader Collencze attacked at his Accommodation in Esteria, Kenetz (town)===
In the town of Kenetz of Esteria where the home of Collencze is established had been under attack by a group referred to as the Heir's from source, no one really understands the principles or purposes of the Heirs however it is understood they are a Guerrilla like Anti-Esterian group with no loyalty to any other nation. They seem to portray conservative principles and anti-socialist principles as their actions are vicious towards the regimen of Esteria. The home was attacked however had been a failure to the Heir's as the security team present and weapons that were provided to the Esterian security team had detered the threat. The accommodation security safeguard the home and the leader Collencze during the attack.</text>
      <sha1>klivuf4ihu6dob1ajj6q2w04aw3zlj6</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Political Spectrum</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2184</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4210</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-08T22:47:02Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;==Political Spectrum==   For those that don't understand politics or what to refer yourself, this is how you distinguish your political reference:    [[File:Left_right_politic...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="201">==Political Spectrum==


For those that don't understand politics or what to refer yourself, this is how you distinguish your political reference:



[[File:Left_right_political_spectrum_011.jpg|left]]</text>
      <sha1>4lirshlzoh5bhozrwtu3rguymrgmj8r</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Populism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2194</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4228</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-14T01:33:06Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:2014-01_cartoon.jpg|thumb|left]]           ==Definition of: Populism==   Populism is a doctrine in politics that appeals the demands of the general populace in the coun...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="745">[[File:2014-01_cartoon.jpg|thumb|left]]










==Definition of: Populism==


Populism is a doctrine in politics that appeals the demands of the general populace in the country. It is based on rhetoric other than realistic principles and can be used as a opportunistic way for xenophobic leaders to gain foothold in power. Populists are as close to the principles of Nazis just at a less extreme level. They exploit the change of beliefs of the populace within the state under economic crisis to obtain their power this way. They are anti-elitist and normally speak on the political rant of being anti-capitalist therefore leaning to some form of fascist or national socialism political development. Populism is found to be very ineffective. </text>
      <sha1>4yccvce5dmarlu24e6ah5qwf53gzlfd</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Propaganda</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2192</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4225</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-14T01:21:05Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Polish-soviet_propaganda_poster_18Y.jpg|thumb|left|214px]]                        ==Definition of: Propaganda==   Propaganda is the concept of political, economical or ...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="790">[[File:Polish-soviet_propaganda_poster_18Y.jpg|thumb|left|214px]]























==Definition of: Propaganda==


Propaganda is the concept of political, economical or commercial advertising to influence to opinion of a collective or group, State propaganda as seen above is mostly common to boost it's support base for it's economic, political or military measures and goals. Extreme presence of propaganda however that is produced by the state can lead the states involved in the process of indoctrination (the act of completey imbedding the life of a populace or person in one collection of information - to brainwash), propaganda and indoctrination can occur for the alteration of the media also known as censorship and the alteration of literature, books, culture and education.</text>
      <sha1>s7bnge5xk4kt5q7snes5yaluocknxqd</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>R.L.F.E.</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2219</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4301</id>
      <timestamp>2014-11-11T10:05:46Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;'''Republican Liberation Front of Esteria'''  This militant group was formed before the revolt, surprisingly a socialist republican militant group that had goaled to achieve p...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="853">'''Republican Liberation Front of Esteria'''

This militant group was formed before the revolt, surprisingly a socialist republican militant group that had goaled to achieve power of Esteria and establish a government and system of democratic centralism. When planning to dissolve once the PPE had established their system of government in the interests of the RLFE (That at the time become a small-militant organization with a drained membership due to the PPE), felt then quickly betrayed as the leader Collencze of the state created a dictatorial authoritarian communist state under his bureaucracy. 

Not entirely funded or well-organized, this organization's member then began to increase steadily after the establishment of the Communist Dictatorship. Through the beginning of the new era, things then began to stay lull for the main developments.</text>
      <sha1>636exxj04ji3dosfdcm343trlv3hbs2</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Republic</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2168</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4171</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-06T02:41:12Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Republic_04.jpg|thumb|left]]                   ==Definition of: Republic==   A republic is a form of government in which no monarchy exists, the power rests with the pe...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1366">[[File:Republic_04.jpg|thumb|left]]


















==Definition of: Republic==


A republic is a form of government in which no monarchy exists, the power rests with the people of the country, whether it be direct or representative democratic rule. Leaders are elected in a Republic rather than inherited or appointed by a superior executive, this providing the power for the populace to choose who to represent them. In a Republic, executive powers are limited to constituion and are restraint by law. In a Republic, laws can only be passed through parliamentry means when legislation is produced by the executive. A republic would also enable popular suffrage in which the people are granted the power to vote the representatives that entitle their demands. However that being said there is forms of Republic governments in which there is oligarchy and aristocracy in which only some rule within power which can exist.

A socialist republic would be highly anti-monarchy by principle however not does not mean Socialist-monarchism is not a hybrid ideology. Socialist Republics are a proletarian form of democracy which are formed from the majority of the time by a revolution. Theocracy and monarchism is strongly opposed by the principles of Marxist Socialism as they are saw as forms of dictatorial rule over the majority class (proletariat or working class).</text>
      <sha1>ss8lihl5tue1n3svin4qjh8r2rp6dud</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Revolution</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2145</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4138</id>
      <parentid>4119</parentid>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T05:19:21Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1797">[[File:1221_Die_Revolution_1848_in_Be.jpg|thumb|left|228px]]


1848 Revolution in Berlin








==Definition of: Revolution ==
Asteron Roleplay - Political Dictionary (Completely improvised by factual knowledge provided by SoldierIR10)

(This has been completely improvised from knowledge, those who claim plagiarism on this articule will have to provide sufficient evidence)

Politically, Revolution basically means the complete fundamental transformation of the system or those in power within a state may it be proletarians(working class/socialists) taken power or the bourgeoisie (business-men/capitalists) or may it just be the general populace over a highly oppressive regime such as a [http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Totalitarian/Totalitarianism totalitarian] one. Revolutions are either motivated by the social and living conditions that the majority class of that state are living are horrendous or to the level of not suitable for living. Revolutions can lead to natural reform of cuture, politics and the behaviour of society depending on the system that is introduced. 

Revolutions are not to get confused with 'coup d'etat's' (see military coup), Revolutions are mainly sourced from a large political collective or the nation or states majority class that are inflicted with repression consistently. Therefore revolutions are justisfied as fundamental when the time comes in which repression becomes to hard and too much upon one class that is the majority. Revolutions are made possible by mass movements and &quot;class conciousness&quot; as talked about by Karl Marx (founder of Modern Socialism), it requires a level of harsh conditions to create a mass revolution such as severe poverty and famine being at it's lowest point in which an imminent revolution can occur.</text>
      <sha1>2ui93gptrh7o7ccvkvled9z0ygtazqd</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Socialism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2158</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4151</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T06:01:29Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Logo.png|thumb|left]]           ==Definition of: Socialism==   Socialism is a economic system of a planned economy in which the free market is abolished in reference to...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1459">[[File:Logo.png|thumb|left]]










==Definition of: Socialism==


Socialism is a economic system of a planned economy in which the free market is abolished in reference to the consistently failing business cycle. A planned economy allows for immediate central government planning of housing, agriculture and production etc. The means of production are moved out of the hands of the capitalist class into the hands of the working class. In Socialism democracy is structured through worker's councils that pose their requirements and demands towards the Central Government. Socialism advocates the abolishment of wage exploitation as found in work places (E.g. If you were a factory making $600 worth of coats, you would only $200 and $400 becomes the boss mans out of your value of labour). Socialism also advocates the principle of the abolishment of private property and monopolization to prevent the growth of elitist corporations that bankrupt middle-class businesses and create wage poverty. 

Socialism advocates the equality of people by treatment from the government and society, that is the only principle of equality there is which is not to be misconcieved as equal payment. Racism, segregation and sectarianism are normally found to be stirred up by elitist politicians that use divide and rule tactics to distract the working class from real economic and social issues. Class hierarchy is demolished under Socialism as a deterant of conflict.</text>
      <sha1>juxc737putn6w4vcqo1lf6sl6p17nsu</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Stalinist Communism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2160</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4155</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T06:14:54Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:Stalin1952.jpg|thumb|left|266px]]               ==Definition of: Stalinist Communism==   The Soviet Union developed from it's Bolshevik fundamentals into a Stalinist bu...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1546">[[File:Stalin1952.jpg|thumb|left|266px]]














==Definition of: Stalinist Communism==


The Soviet Union developed from it's Bolshevik fundamentals into a Stalinist bureaucracy, Joseph Stalin manifested his own idea of communist by developing the idea of communist while using the growth of Socialism and so that the people would become accepting to Communist by the use of terror and authoritarianism. Under Stalinism there is oppressive collectivization which is a agriculture system of revoking the ability for peasant farmers to havest crops and then sell them, instead peasant farmers were to work for the state by harvesting the crops and having them divided among the populace. Stalinism also advocates rapid industrialization to expand the class of the workers. Industries being the main reason for the creation of a working class in the first place, becoming a necessary requirement for the build of socialism.

Stalinist Communist would take violent measures towards bourgeoisie society by attempting to eradicate it, by conclusion Stalinist Communist is a form of using terror to enforce and speed up the development of Communism by having people accept it oppressively. Stalin was mentally ill of paranoia, insanity and feeling that he was always being targetted, any anti-state or anti-Stalin talk among individuals and those individuals were removed and deemed as enemies of the state. This being justification that this is not the pure workings of socialism or communism, more than a political failure than an economic one.</text>
      <sha1>lc06dhix7qk2elqxmfit8v8wjhwf50v</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Totalitarian/Totalitarianism</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2147</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4121</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-05T04:00:59Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;[[File:North_korea_parade-ttyv.jpg|thumb|left|284px]]                  ==Definition of: Totalitarianism==   Totalitarianism is a condition implemented by an autocratic governm...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="1310">[[File:North_korea_parade-ttyv.jpg|thumb|left|284px]]

















==Definition of: Totalitarianism==


Totalitarianism is a condition implemented by an autocratic government or system. Regimes that want to create war machines through total war production, military education and the teachings of eugeneics and euthanasia, social darwinism and so on as inherited from the first fascist regimes. It is also a method of intervening into people's everyday lives by pressuring and authoritarianly forcing workers and the populace to work for the good of the state in hard labour without the abilty to protest or complain on the conditions. This may be private or public life, it may not matter the state will maintain authoritarian control over the populace or may even regulate the opinion of the populace by the use of secret police, and domestic espionage to persecute any anti-state defectors.

The use of totalitarianism even though being very oppressive to the extent of reaction, when applied with the use of domestic espionage and secret police, resistance is made almost physically impossible in someways and requires another nation to aid it's downfall as seen in Nazi Germany with the likes of a district system led by the Gestapo secret police, the likes of the Cheka of the Stalinist Soviet Union.</text>
      <sha1>lti6kh1lzpjjyhx2cp89pn73mvrxzfj</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Wiki Content</title>
    <ns>0</ns>
    <id>2173</id>
    <revision>
      <id>4179</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-06T04:00:47Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>SoldierIR10</username>
        <id>25018445</id>
      </contributor>
      <comment>Created page with &quot;==Content A-RP:==   [http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Nations NATIONS [SECTION]]  [http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Characters CHARACTERS [SECT...&quot;</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="487">==Content A-RP:==


[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Nations NATIONS [SECTION]]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Characters CHARACTERS [SECTION]]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Militant_Organizations MILITANT ORGANIZATIONS [SECTION]]

[http://asteron-roleplay-minecraft.wikia.com/wiki/Mini_Dictionary MINI-DICTIONARY [SECTION]]


===This page is just a content menu of this wikia - it contains the necessary information sections.===</text>
      <sha1>8tlfc1ghdknbiz076brfz9sjb63fa9n</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Template:!</title>
    <ns>10</ns>
    <id>2076</id>
    <revision>
      <id>3654</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-04T17:37:30Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>Default</username>
        <id>49312</id>
      </contributor>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="46">&lt;onlyinclude&gt;|&lt;/onlyinclude&gt;
{{documentation}}</text>
      <sha1>482k5k6o1iym676dzqlo6yfmyo0tlel</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
  <page>
    <title>Template:Infobox character</title>
    <ns>10</ns>
    <id>2115</id>
    <revision>
      <id>3941</id>
      <timestamp>2014-07-04T17:37:30Z</timestamp>
      <contributor>
        <username>Default</username>
        <id>49312</id>
      </contributor>
      <minor/>
      <comment>1 revision</comment>
      <text xml:space="preserve" bytes="929">&lt;onlyinclude&gt;{| class=&quot;wikia-infobox&quot;

|-
! class=&quot;wikia-infobox-header&quot; colspan=&quot;2&quot; | {{{title|''Unknown''}}}

|-
{{#if: {{{image|}}} |
{{!}} class=&quot;wikia-infobox-image&quot; colspan=&quot;2&quot; {{!}} [[File:{{{image}}}|{{{imagewidth|210}}}px|{{{imagecaption|}}}]]
| }}

|-
{{#if: {{{imagecaption|}}} |
{{!}} class=&quot;wikia-infobox-caption&quot; colspan=&quot;2&quot; {{!}} {{{imagecaption}}}
| }}

|-
! colspan=&quot;2&quot; | &lt;div class=&quot;wikia-infobox-section-header&quot;&gt;Vital statistics&lt;/div&gt;

|-
! Position
| {{{position|''Unknown''}}}

|-
! Age
| {{{age|''Unknown''}}}

|-
! Status
| {{{status|''Unknown''}}}

|-
! colspan=&quot;2&quot; | &lt;div class=&quot;wikia-infobox-section-header&quot;&gt;Physical attributes&lt;/div&gt;

|-
! Height
| {{{height|''Unknown''}}}

|-
! Weight
| {{{weight|''Unknown''}}}

|- style=&quot;font-size:0; line-height:0;&quot;
! style=&quot;width:50%; padding:0&quot; |
! style=&quot;width:50%; padding:0&quot; |

|}&lt;/onlyinclude&gt;&lt;noinclude&gt;&lt;br style=&quot;clear:both;&quot;/&gt;
{{documentation}}&lt;/noinclude&gt;</text>
      <sha1>9en99nzvjherbyahkoqtm3kzwvzyi5z</sha1>
    </revision>
  </page>
</mediawiki>
